There are a
lot of ways to find content on your site.
One way is to just find it
on the front end like a user would.
If you're looking for a news item
that was, created recently,
you can find it in the news list.
Another way is to just search for it
on the front end.
And we can find it there.
Another way is to go to your dashboard
and each of these blocks,
you know, we have on the news block.
The events block, the media block.
If you click down at the bottom, one more,
you're going to get all the news
and you can search it as well.
Now, if all else fails,
the most powerful way
to, find content is to go to content.
And this is the content management
overview.
You can see that
we have several different, tabs
where we can narrow down on, on content,
or we can search for it right here.
We can sort
newest, oldest.
We can look for stuff that's unpublished.
We can look for stuff by content type.
So if I only want to departments
that contain admin,
there's the administration department.